Hello friends, you are
very welcome to the market.  Friends, in this video we will
talk about the results of ICICI LBD Quarter Two.
So please subscribe to the channel.  If you
like it, please
like the video.  So friends, let's go here and talk
about the company's quarter 2 results.
So friends, first of all let us talk about
any update where
such bonus dividend is seen from the company
or not.  So you can see
that if we start first of all, then
here we get to see the news of
any dividend bonus,
so this is the specialty of our channel that it first of all
informs you about the dividend in this manner especially with
proof, so you can see that the company
ICICI PB has announced the interim dividend here,
here you shareholders are going to get a dividend of ₹6.50 per share
and according to 65% interest and
₹10 face value, you are getting
to see it here.  Now let's talk about what the date is going to be.
So
friends, the record date here has been
fixed here.
If you buy this stock before October 23rd, you may be
eligible for this dividend.  So let us
talk about when will it come into your account?
So friends, a date is also given here
that this will become payable in your account
around 12th November.  You will get the
dividend per share of the company in your account
here around 12th November.
Now let's talk about
what results we are seeing as per the company's balance sheet for quarter two.
So
here you can see the company's quarter two results.
Talking about the amount,
we will talk in lakhs and crores, which
if you can see, the
operating results are mentioned here.  Where
gross premium, net premium, whatever is the
income of the company is
mentioned here.  We will talk about
total income here, which means that after adding all these,
how much total income of the company is
seen, so
if you see the total income of last year here, which was
in lakhs of rupees, then we are going to talk in crores,
you can see the total income of the company last year, it was
around 5850 crores, which has increased this time to
6582 crores, here the income of the company is
seen increasing, which
shows that the result of the company is fine here, that is, it is
seen fine here, if we
talk about the last quarter,
what is happening now as per quarter one, then the
income of the company was around 683 crores,
we can see that it is increasing in this quarter also, so
here the total income of the
company is seen increasing year on year, quarter to quarter, if we
talk about the expenses, what is the total expenses
seen this year from last year,
last year the total expenses of the company were
around 5186 crores, which  That
this time it is increasing a little because the
income of the company is increasing, so Rs 5830 crores are
seen going here.
In the last quarter, it was seen around Rs 54.29 crore.
So
you can see the total expenses of this company increasing like this.
Because here the
company's income was also seen increasing.
Now let's talk about the profit loss of the company.
So if you see here, if I
take the profit of the company a little below here, then
if you see the final profit here, the
net profit after tax is
mentioned here which you can see.  So
last year the profit of the company was
around Rs 693 crore.  So here
it has increased from 693 to 815 crores.  So
we are seeing this upside.  Here, we can
say that the company is seeing growth of around 20%.
If we
talk about the last quarter, the
company had a profit of Rs 764 crore in the last quarter.  It can be said that
here the profit of the company can be seen increasing by more than 6.5%.
Then it is seen increasing year on year and quarter to
quarter.
So here, looking at the company's results, we
can almost clearly say that
we are seeing an upside in profit.
Meaning, if we talk about the company's shares here, the
chances of a positive result are
higher.  Where if we talk about Pay Plus, if we
talk about the EPS of the company, then here
you can see the EPS of the company,
what was seen this year from last year
?  So here I will tell you a little bit about it
basically in two ways
which you can see.  Here I am
zooming in a little and showing you.  So
last year within quarter two it was around
13.88 and it
said something while doing basic and daily.  So here I am
telling you the basics.  It was around 14 points
last year.  This time it
increased by 16 points.
It was by 15 points in the last quarter.  So year on
year and quarter to quarter, the
EPS is seen increasing very well,
so we are seeing the results of ICICI Lar very
positive and if
seen according to the results, then we can see this stock at a good
level.  So just
subscribe to the channel here for the results of quarter three.  Thank you